imbahost.com 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy - MightWeb - Pure SSD Hosting - Web Hosting, VPS and Dedicated Servers

## These policies govern how we handle your personal information as a client of ours and user of our services

## Last updated: May 24, 2018

## Relander Group Inc ("us", "we", "MightWeb", "Relander Group", "Relander Group Inc" or "our") operates the https://mightweb.net website and any services listed on any website in affiliation with MightWeb (the "Service").

## We may collect and receive information about users of our Services ("users," "you," or "your") from various sources, including Information you provide through your user account on the Services (your "Account") if you register for the Services; Your use of the Services; and from third-party websites, services, and partners.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at <https://mightweb.net/terms-of-service/>

## We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy in full. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or MightWeb's data collection, use please contact us

**Your personal information, and how we handle it**

With your personal information, we refer to the data we collect and save you, and how you utilize the services we provide, that directly or indirectly identifies you. We use this data to provide service, give you a better experience using our services, and give you offers that are relevant to you.

Below, we have collected a summary of information about how we collect and handle your personal information in accordance with the [General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://gdpr-info.eu/)

01-

### Information That You Provide Us

I. Account Sign Up. When you register for an Account, we will ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.

II. Payment Information. When you add your financial account information to your Account, that information is directed to our third-party payment processor(s). We do not store your financial account information on our systems; however, we have access to and may retain, subscriber information through our third-party payment processor(s).

III. Communications. If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide. We may also receive a confirmation when you open an email from us.  
The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

02-

### Information We Collect When You Use Our Services.

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

I. When you use our Services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, landing page, and referring URL. To collect this information, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Services. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognize you. We store information that we collect through cookies We may also automatically collect information about your use of features of our Services, about the functionality of our Services, frequency of visits, and other information related to your interactions with the Services.

II. Usage of our Services. When you use our Services, we may collect information about your engagement with and utilization of our Services, such as processor and memory usage, storage capacity, navigation of our Services, and system-level metrics. We use this data to operate the Services, maintain and improve the performance and utilization of the Services, develop new features, protect the security and safety of our Services and our customers, and provide customer support. We also use this data to develop business intelligence that enables us to operate, protect, make informed decisions, and report on the performance of our business.

03-

### How we use the identifiable information

For us to maintain your data, it is required that at least one of the below applies  
• It is required for us to fulfill our agreement with you  
• It is required for MightWeb to fulfill a binding legal agreement  
• The maintaining of the data is in both yours, and MightWeb’s interest  
• Expressed consent from you for the maintaining of that specific data

For us to provide our services to you, we need to maintain your personal information. Below, you’ll find a more in-depth review of what we use this data for, as well as what legal basis that uses is justified by.

 **To provide services**

We store and maintain personal information to identify you as a customer and manage/deliver the services you have ordered and subscribe to. We also store the information required to handle billing and payments for the services you use.

We may use information from previous instances where you’ve contacted us, in order to provide a better and more tailored experience. We use your contact information, as well as information about what services you use as a basis for invoices, newsletters, important communication about your services, promotional material, as well as tips/help about how to use our services.

 **Product/Service Development**

We use information regarding how you utilize our services, as well as contact with us, as a basis for improving your experience specifically, and our services in general.

 **Marketing**

For us to market relevant products and services to you, based on your needs, we maintain information about what services you use and how you use them.

 **Security and Abuse Prevention**

We use identifiable information to find and prevent abuse of our services and to maintain the integrity of our network. More specifically, we use it to prevent violations of our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy, direct attacks (for example DDoS or brute force attacks) and violations of governing law.

 **Requirements by governing law**  
We maintain information to comply with governing law. We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

04-

### How long we store your information

Depending on the nature of the information, the time it is stored may vary. In short, however, no data is stored longer than there is justifiable cause to maintain that data.

05-

### Why and How we share your information

Our agreements with partners may sometimes require that we share identifiable information. Our agreements with these third parties regulate how this data is to be protected, and for how long it may be maintained. In all cases, data is to be maintained no longer than there is justifiable cause to maintain said data.

Our goal is to never share more information than what is necessary with any third party. We make efforts to ensure that the information shared is treated in accordance with applicable law regarding safety and personal integrity. This is a requirement for any third party we work with.

 **Marketing and Analysis**

 **Google Analytics** – data through third party cookies for marketing and web analytics in order to improve our services. http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/

 **Service Delivery**

 **WHMCS** – URL/Domain and Installation Path for WHMCS Installations.

 **Microsoft** – IP Address, Hostname and MAC Address for Windows Server Installations.

 **cPanel** – Account names, log data and any data stored by you as an end user, on cPanel powered systems, on a strictly as-required basis, for troubleshooting.

 **OpenSRS** – Identifiable information that is required to register/renew and manage domain names.

 **NetEarthOne** – Identifiable information that is required to register/renew and manage domain names.

 **Enom** – Identifiable information that is required to register/renew and manage domain names.

 **LiteSpeed Technologies** – Account names, log data and any data stored by you as an end user, on LiteSpeed powered systems, on a strictly as-required basis, for troubleshooting.

 **SpamExperts** – Identifiable information tied to e-mail delivery for end users that opt to use SpamExperts services. Includes full mail headers.

 **CloudLinux** – Account names, log data and any data stored by you as an end user, on cPanel powered systems, on a strictly as-required basis, for troubleshooting.

 **Tawk.to Verloop** – Live chat programs that track user’s browser and site activity for purposes of marketing and troubleshooting customer related issues

 **Payment Processing**

 **PayPal** – Identifiable information including name, address, e-mail address, PayPal account e-mail address, transaction ID’s, IP Address, and Invoice ID’s as required to process payments via PayPal.

 **Stripe** – Identifiable information including name, address, e-mail address, credit card information, transaction ID’s as required to process a credit card payment via Stripe.

 **Governments or Government Identities**  
Upon a lawful order, we may be required to pass identifiable information to these entities, for example to Law Enforcement upon a court order.

06-

### How we protect your identifiable information

We make use of best industry practices to safely store, maintain and communicate identifiable information such as personal information and passwords in a secure way. This protection is implemented with systematic, organizational and technical measures to ensure integrity, secrecy, and availability are maintained.  
MightWeb staff is bound to never disclose your personal information except for as permitted and required. Staff access to identifiable information is strictly controlled, meaning no one has access to more information than required to fulfill their specific duties.

07-

### You control your personal information

Your personal information is yours and is under your control. You decide which information you wish to share, you decide how that information may be maintained, and you can at any point in time cancel your consent to store this data. Note however that we need certain information to provide our services. Cancelling your consent may render us unable to provide certain services to you.  
Upon cancellation of your account, we delete information if there is no further purpose for this data to be maintained. Normally, unless you cancel your expressed consent, this means we delete the data six months past your cancellation. We also notify any partners to whom your data has been shared to delete this data. Note that some information (such as payment information) may be kept for an extended period to comply with tax law. This information is to be kept as minimal as possible.

08-

### Personal information when MightWeb acts as a processor

In the case where MightWeb acts as a processor, and you as an individual or your company is the controller, our treatment of identifiable information is regulated by our Data Controller Agreement (Agreement link to be posted when available)  
This is applicable, for example, when you run a web shop, or use Reseller Hosting services – where the information is stored on MightWeb servers, but the collection is done by you as an individual or your company.

09-

### Links to other sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

10-

### Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).  
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

11-

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

12-

### International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States of America and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States of America and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

13-

### Data Protection

We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists.

14-

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, or wish for any details stored about you to be removed or edited, please contact us.

15-

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

We use cookies to ensure the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site you agree to the use of cookies. Accept [Read More](https://mightweb.net/privacy-policy)
